When are you gonna stop
making Cylon toast?
(Sheldon:)When I have enough to destroy
the human toast...
(Sheldon:)...on the Battlestar
known as Galactica.
(Sheldon:)Is that what you're wearing
to watch football?
(Leonard:)-What's wrong with a football jersey?
-Nothing.
(Sheldon:)That, however,
appears to be a football cocktail dress.
It's the smallest size they had.
(Leonard:)Except the one for dogs.
(Leonard:)I can't believe they had one for dogs.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes. Canine football fans
are a common sight in Texas.
(Sheldon:)Cats, however,
refuse to wear sporting apparel.
(Sheldon:)My sister found that out the hard way.
(Leonard:)-Anyway, wish me luck.
-Leonard, wait.